{
  "catagory": {
    "analytics": [
      {
        "question": "Query Data in S3 using SQL",
        "answer": "Amazon Athena",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS Glue",
          "AWS Data Exchange",
          "Amazon Redshift"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Managed Search Service",
        "answer": "Amazon CloudSearch",
        "distractors": [
          "Amazon Rekognition",
          "AWS App Mesh",
          "AWS Cloud Map"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Run and Scale OpenSearch Clusters",
        "answer": "Amazon OpenSearch Service",
        "distractors": [
          "Amazon RDS on VMware",
          "AWS Data Pipeline",
          "AWS Database Migration Service"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Hosted Hadoop Framework",
        "answer": "Amazon EMR",
        "distractors": [
          "Amazon GameLift",
          "Amazon Athena",
          "Amazon Simple Email Service (SES)"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Work with Real-time Streaming Data",
        "answer": "Amazon Kinesis",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS Cloud Map",
          "AWS CodeBuild",
          "AWS IoT Device Management"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Fast Business Analytics Service",
        "answer": "Amazon QuickSight",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS PrivateLink",
          "Amazon Connect",
          "Amazon API Gateway"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Find, subscribe to, and use third-party data in the cloud",
        "answer": "AWS Data Exchange",
        "distractors": [
          "Amazon Athena",
          "AWS Secrets Manager",
          "Amazon CloudSearch"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Orchestration Service for Periodic, Data-driven Workflows",
        "answer": "AWS Data Pipeline",
        "distractors": [
          "Amazon AppSync",
          "AWS Database Migration Service",
          "Amazon Lumberyard"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Prepare and Load Data",
        "answer": "AWS Glue",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS Migration Hub",
          "Amazon Quantum Ledger Database (QLDB)",
          "Amazon DocumentDB (with MongoDB compatibility)"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Build a secure data lake in days",
        "answer": "AWS Lake Formation",
        "distractors": [
          "Amazon Elastic Inference",
          "AWS Direct Connect",
          "AWS Cost Explorer"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "ML-based service for matching and linking records across datasets",
        "answer": "AWS Entity Resolution",
        "distractors": [
          "Amazon Athena",
          "AWS Glue",
          "Amazon Personalize"
        ]
      }
      ,
      {
        "question": "Serverless data integration service",
        "answer": "Amazon AppFlow",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS Glue",
          "Amazon Kinesis",
          "AWS Data Pipeline"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Managed service for Apache Airflow",
        "answer": "Amazon Managed Workflows for Apache Airflow (MWAA)",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS Data Pipeline",
          "AWS Step Functions",
          "AWS Glue"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Serverless option for running EMR jobs",
        "answer": "Amazon EMR Serverless",
        "distractors": [
          "Amazon EMR",
          "Amazon Athena",
          "AWS Batch"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Financial services data and analytics service",
        "answer": "Amazon FinSpace",
        "distractors": [
          "Amazon Quicksight",
          "AWS Data Exchange",
          "Amazon Redshift"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Managed service for genomic analysis and storage",
        "answer": "Amazon Omics",
        "distractors": [
          "Amazon HealthLake",
          "AWS Glue",
          "Amazon Redshift"
        ]
      }
    ],
    "ar_and_vr": [
      {
        "question": "Build and Run VR and AR Applications",
        "answer": "Amazon Sumerian",
        "distractors": [
          "Amazon Timestream",
          "Amazon Corretto",
          "AWS Command Line Interface"
        ]
      }
    ],
    "containers_and_orchestration": [
      {
        "question": "Fully managed service for running containerized web applications",
        "answer": "AWS App Runner",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS Fargate",
          "Amazon ECS",
          "AWS Proton"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Kubernetes distribution maintained by AWS",
        "answer": "Amazon EKS Distro",
        "distractors": [
          "Amazon Elastic Kubernetes Service",
          "AWS Bottlerocket",
          "Amazon EC2"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Linux-based operating system purpose-built for running containers",
        "answer": "AWS Bottlerocket",
        "distractors": [
          "Amazon Linux",
          "AWS Greengrass",
          "Amazon AMI"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "CLI tool to build and deploy containerized apps to AWS",
        "answer": "AWS Copilot",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS CLI",
          "AWS SAM",
          "AWS CloudFormation"
        ]
      }
    ],
    "serverless": [
      {
        "question": "Run Lambda functions at AWS Edge locations (CloudFront)",
        "answer": "Lambda@Edge",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS Wavelength",
          "CloudFront Functions",
          "AWS App Runner"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Deploy and manage container and serverless services with opinionated infrastructure",
        "answer": "AWS Proton",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS Elastic Beanstalk",
          "AWS CloudFormation",
          "AWS App Runner"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Framework for building serverless applications",
        "answer": "AWS SAM",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS CDK",
          "AWS CloudFormation",
          "AWS Serverless Application Repository"
        ]
      }
    ],
    "observability": [
      {
        "question": "Managed Grafana service for visualization and dashboards",
        "answer": "Amazon Managed Grafana",
        "distractors": [
          "Amazon CloudWatch",
          "AWS X-Ray",
          "Datadog"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Chaos engineering service to run fault injection experiments",
        "answer": "AWS Fault Injection Simulator",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS Systems Manager",
          "AWS Config",
          "AWS Shield"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "AI-powered operational insights for your applications",
        "answer": "Amazon DevOps Guru",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS X-Ray",
          "Amazon CloudWatch",
          "AWS CloudTrail"
        ]
      }
    ],
    "application_integration": [
      {
        "question": "Query Data in S3 using SQL",
        "answer": "Amazon Athena",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS Glue",
          "AWS Data Exchange",
          "Amazon Redshift"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Managed Search Service",
        "answer": "Amazon CloudSearch",
        "distractors": [
          "Amazon Rekognition",
          "AWS App Mesh",
          "AWS Cloud Map"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Run and Scale OpenSearch Clusters",
        "answer": "Amazon OpenSearch Service",
        "distractors": [
          "Amazon Transcribe",
          "AWS Cost Explorer",
          "AWS Budgets"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Hosted Hadoop Framework",
        "answer": "Amazon EMR",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS IoT Analytics",
          "Amazon Detective",
          "AWS Elemental Appliances & Software"
        ]
      },

      {
        "question": "Build, deploy, and manage GraphQL APIs",
        "answer": "AWS AppSync",
        "distractors": [
          "Amazon API Gateway",
          "AWS App Mesh",
          "AWS Amplify"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Work with Real-time Streaming Data",
        "answer": "Amazon Kinesis",
        "distractors": [
          "Amazon Transcribe",
          "Amazon MQ",
          "AWS App Mesh"
        ]
      }
    ],

    "aws_cost_management": [
      {
        "question": "Analyze Your AWS Cost and Usage",
        "answer": "AWS Cost Explorer",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS Budgets",
          "AWS Trusted Advisor",
          "AWS Cost and Usage Report"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Set Custom Cost and Usage Budgets",
        "answer": "AWS Budgets",
        "distractors": [
          "Amazon OpenSearch Service",
          "AWS IoT Device Management",
          "Amazon FreeRTOS"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Access Comprehensive Cost and Usage Information",
        "answer": "AWS Cost and Usage Report",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS Secrets Manager",
          "AWS Lambda",
          "AWS Lake Formation"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Dive Deeper into Your Reserved Instances (RIs)",
        "answer": "Reserved Instance Reporting",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS X-Ray",
          "AWS CodeBuild",
          "AWS Deep Learning AMIs"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Save up to 72% on compute usage with flexible pricing",
        "answer": "Savings Plans",
        "distractors": [
          "EC2 Spot Instances",
          "AWS Cost Explorer",
          "Reserved Instance Reporting"
        ]
      }
    ],
    "blockchain": [
      {
        "question": "Create and manage scalable blockchain networks",
        "answer": "Amazon Managed Blockchain",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS CloudFormation",
          "Amazon Kinesis",
          "Amazon CloudWatch"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Fully managed ledger database",
        "answer": "Amazon Quantum Ledger Database (QLDB)",
        "distractors": [
          "Amazon ElastiCache",
          "Amazon Fraud Detector",
          "AWS Command Line Interface"
        ]
      }
    ],
    "business_applications": [
      {
        "question": "Empower your Organization with Alexa",
        "answer": "Alexa for Business",
        "distractors": [
          "Amazon OpenSearch Service",
          "Amazon Redshift",
          "AWS IoT Device Management"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Frustration-free Meetings, Video Calls, and Chat",
        "answer": "Amazon Chime",
        "distractors": [
          "Amazon AppStream 2.0",
          "Amazon Elastic Transcoder",
          "AWS Outposts"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Secure enterprise document storage and sharing",
        "answer": "Amazon WorkDocs",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS Command Line Interface",
          "AWS Compute Optimizer",
          "AWS Ground Station"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Secure and Managed Business Email and Calendaring",
        "answer": "Amazon WorkMail",
        "distractors": [
          "Amazon Athena",
          "AWS IoT 1-Click",
          "AWS Deep Learning Containers"
        ]
      }
    ],
    "compute": [
      {
        "question": "Virtual Servers in the Cloud",
        "answer": "Amazon EC2",
        "distractors": [
          "Amazon WorkDocs",
          "Amazon EMR",
          "Amazon MQ"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Scale Compute Capacity to Meet Demand",
        "answer": "Amazon EC2 Auto Scaling",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS Cloud Map",
          "Amazon Redshift",
          "Amazon Elastic Container Registry"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Store and Retrieve Docker Images",
        "answer": "Amazon Elastic Container Registry",
        "distractors": [
          "Amazon CloudSearch",
          "Amazon Transcribe",
          "AWS Data Exchange"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Run and Manage Docker Containers",
        "answer": "Amazon Elastic Container Service",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS X-Ray",
          "AWS Trusted Advisor",
          "Amazon Redshift"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Run Managed Kubernetes on AWS",
        "answer": "Amazon Elastic Kubernetes Service",
        "distractors": [
          "Amazon ECS",
          "Amazon Aurora",
          "Amazon Lightsail"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Launch and Manage Virtual Private Servers",
        "answer": "Amazon Lightsail",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS DeepRacer",
          "Amazon Elastic Block Store (EBS)",
          "AWS Inferentia2"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Run Batch Jobs at Any Scale",
        "answer": "AWS Batch",
        "distractors": [
          "Amazon Athena",
          "Amazon MQ",
          "AWS Well-Architected Tool"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Run and Manage Web Apps",
        "answer": "AWS Elastic Beanstalk",
        "distractors": [
          "Apache MXNet on AWS",
          "AWS Ground Station",
          "AWS Auto Scaling"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Run Containers without Managing Servers or Clusters",
        "answer": "AWS Fargate",
        "distractors": [
          "Amazon WorkMail",
          "AWS Server Migration Service",
          "Amazon MQ"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Run your Code in Response to Events",
        "answer": "AWS Lambda",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS Elemental MediaPackage",
          "Amazon WorkDocs",
          "Amazon EMR"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Run AWS services on-premises",
        "answer": "AWS Outposts",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS Elemental MediaStore",
          "Amazon Elastic Kubernetes Service",
          "AWS CodeBuild"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Discover, Deploy, and Publish Serverless Applications",
        "answer": "AWS Serverless Application Repository",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS RoboMaker",
          "AWS Artifact",
          "AWS Identity & Access Management"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Deliver ultra-low latency edge computing for 5G devices",
        "answer": "AWS Wavelength",
        "distractors": [
          "Amazon Elastic Inference",
          "Amazon Managed Streaming for Apache Kafka",
          "Amazon Macie"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Build a Hybrid Cloud without Custom Hardware",
        "answer": "VMware Cloud on AWS",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS Elastic Beanstalk",
          "AWS CodePipeline",
          "AWS CloudFormation"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "ARM-based processors for EC2 instances",
        "answer": "AWS Graviton (Graviton3/Graviton4)",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS Inferentia2",
          "AWS Trainium (Trainium2)",
          "AWS Habana Gaudi"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Run Kubernetes on-premises",
        "answer": "Amazon EKS Anywhere",
        "distractors": [
          "Amazon ECS Anywhere",
          "AWS Outposts",
          "AWS App Runner"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Serverless compute with spot pricing",
        "answer": "AWS Fargate Spot",
        "distractors": [
          "EC2 Spot Instances",
          "AWS Lambda",
          "AWS Batch"
        ]
      }
    ],
    "customer_engagement": [
      {
        "question": "Cloud-based Contact Center",
        "answer": "Amazon Connect",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS IoT SiteWise",
          "Amazon QuickSight",
          "Amazon CloudSearch"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Personalized User Engagement Across Channels",
        "answer": "Amazon Pinpoint",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS RoboMaker",
          "Amazon ElastiCache",
          "Amazon WorkSpaces"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Email Sending and Receiving",
        "answer": "Amazon Simple Email Service (SES)",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS Secrets Manager",
          "TensorFlow on AWS",
          "AWS Compute Optimizer"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "ML-powered contact center analytics",
        "answer": "Contact Lens for Amazon Connect",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS Console Mobile Application",
          "AWS Application Discovery Service",
          "Amazon AppSync"
        ]
      }
    ],
    "database": [
      {
        "question": "High Performance Managed Relational Database",
        "answer": "Amazon Aurora",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS Greengrass",
          "Amazon Cognito",
          "Amazon Kinesis"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Managed NoSQL Database",
        "answer": "Amazon DynamoDB",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS Direct Connect",
          "AWS IoT Analytics",
          "Amazon AppStream 2.0"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Fully managed document database",
        "answer": "Amazon DocumentDB (with MongoDB compatibility)",
        "distractors": [
          "Amazon OpenSearch Service",
          "Amazon Redshift",
          "Amazon Elastic Kubernetes Service"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "In-memory Caching System",
        "answer": "Amazon ElastiCache",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS Application Discovery Service",
          "Amazon S3 Glacier",
          "AWS Migration Hub"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Managed Apache Cassandra-compatible database",
        "answer": "Amazon Keyspaces (for Apache Cassandra)",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS Tools and SDKs",
          "AWS App Mesh",
          "AWS DeepRacer"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Fully Managed Graph Database Service",
        "answer": "Amazon Neptune",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS IoT 1-Click",
          "AWS Identity & Access Management",
          "AWS Data Pipeline"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Fully managed ledger database",
        "answer": "Amazon Quantum Ledger Database (QLDB)",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS IoT Device Defender",
          "AWS Data Pipeline",
          "Amazon Corretto"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Managed Relational Database Service for MySQL, PostgreSQL, Oracle, SQL Server, and MariaDB",
        "answer": "Amazon RDS",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS CodeCommit",
          "AWS Data Pipeline",
          "Amazon Polly"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Automate on-premises database management",
        "answer": "Amazon RDS on VMware",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS Elemental MediaStore",
          "AWS Systems Manager",
          "AWS Snow Family"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Fast, Simple, Cost-effective Data Warehousing",
        "answer": "Amazon Redshift",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS CodeBuild",
          "Amazon SageMaker Ground Truth",
          "AWS Tools and SDKs"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Fully managed time series database for real-time analytics (InfluxDB compatibility)",
        "answer": "Amazon Timestream",
        "distractors": [
          "Amazon CloudSearch",
          "Amazon EMR",
          "AWS DeepRacer"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Migrate Databases with Minimal Downtime",
        "answer": "AWS Database Migration Service",
        "distractors": [
          "Amazon Athena",
          "Amazon Simple Storage Service (S3)",
          "AWS IoT 1-Click"
        ]
      }
    ],
    "developer_tools": [
      {
        "question": "Production-ready distribution of OpenJDK",
        "answer": "Amazon Corretto",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS License Manager",
          "Amazon AppSync",
          "AWS Direct Connect"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Model cloud infrastructure using code",
        "answer": "AWS Cloud Development Kit (CDK)",
        "distractors": [
          "Amazon Kinesis Video Streams",
          "Amazon CloudWatch",
          "AWS DataSync"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Write, Run, and Debug Code on a Cloud IDE",
        "answer": "AWS Cloud9",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS Transit Gateway",
          "AWS Tools and SDKs",
          "AWS Data Pipeline"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Build and Test Code",
        "answer": "AWS CodeBuild",
        "distractors": [
          "Amazon EC2",
          "Elastic Load Balancing",
          "Amazon CodeGuru"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Store Code in Private Git Repositories",
        "answer": "AWS CodeCommit",
        "distractors": [
          "Amazon OpenSearch Service",
          "Apache MXNet on AWS",
          "Amazon Chime"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Automate Code Deployment",
        "answer": "AWS CodeDeploy",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS Ground Station",
          "AWS Tools and SDKs",
          "AWS CodePipeline"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Release Software using Continuous Deliver",
        "answer": "AWS CodePipeline",
        "distractors": [
          "Amazon Kendra",
          "AWS Management Console",
          "AWS Lambda"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Develop and Deploy AWS Applications",
        "answer": "AWS CodeStar",
        "distractors": [
          "Amazon Quantum Ledger Database (QLDB)",
          "Amazon EMR",
          "AWS Global Accelerator"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Unified Tool to Manage AWS Services",
        "answer": "AWS Command Line Interface",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS RoboMaker",
          "Amazon EMR",
          "AWS Cloud9"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Test Android, iOS, and web apps on real devices in the AWS cloud",
        "answer": "AWS Device Farm",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS Cloud Map",
          "Amazon Cognito",
          "AWS Step Functions"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Tools and SDKs for AWS",
        "answer": "AWS Tools and SDKs",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS Lambda",
          "Contact Lens for Amazon Connect",
          "Amazon Textract"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Analyze and debug your applications",
        "answer": "AWS X-Ray",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS Elemental MediaConvert",
          "Amazon CloudSearch",
          "VMware Cloud on AWS"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "AI-powered assistant for code, data, and AWS services",
        "answer": "Amazon Q",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS Trusted Advisor",
          "Amazon Transcribe",
          "AWS Step Functions"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "AI code completion and recommendation tool",
        "answer": "Amazon CodeWhisperer",
        "distractors": [
          "Amazon Kendra",
          "AWS CodeDeploy",
          "AWS Chatbot"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Visual builder for serverless applications",
        "answer": "AWS Application Composer",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS CloudFormation",
          "AWS Lambda",
          "Amazon Comprehend"
        ]
      }
    ],
    "end_user_computing": [
      {
        "question": "Stream Desktop Applications Securely to a Browser",
        "answer": "Amazon AppStream 2.0",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS Deep Learning Containers",
          "Amazon Kinesis",
          "Amazon Athena"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Secure enterprise document storage and sharing",
        "answer": "Amazon WorkDocs",
        "distractors": [
          "Amazon Simple Storage Service (S3)",
          "Amazon Neptune",
          "Amazon Kinesis"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Enable mobile access to internal websites",
        "answer": "Amazon WorkLink",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS Systems Manager",
          "AWS Artifact",
          "AWS Amplify"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Desktop Computing Service",
        "answer": "Amazon WorkSpaces",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS IoT Events",
          "TensorFlow on AWS",
          "AWS Elemental MediaTailor"
        ]
      }
    ],
    "game_tech": [
      {
        "question": "Simple, Fast, Cost-effective Dedicated Game Server Hosting",
        "answer": "Amazon GameLift",
        "distractors": [
          "Amazon Route 53",
          "Amazon Macie",
          "Amazon MQ"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "A Free Cross-platform 3D Game Engine with Full Source, Integrated with AWS and Twitch",
        "answer": "Amazon Lumberyard",
        "distractors": [
          "Amazon WorkMail",
          "AWS PrivateLink",
          "CloudEndure Migration"
        ]
      }
    ],
    "internet_of_things": [
      {
        "question": "Connect Devices to the Cloud",
        "answer": "AWS IoT Core",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS Tools and SDKs",
          "AWS Directory Service",
          "AWS Global Accelerator"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "IoT Operating System for Microcontrollers",
        "answer": "Amazon FreeRTOS",
        "distractors": [
          "Amazon CloudSearch",
          "AWS Ground Station",
          "Amazon Athena"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Local Compute, Messaging, and Sync for Devices",
        "answer": "AWS Greengrass",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS Console Mobile Application",
          "AWS Data Exchange",
          "Amazon SageMaker"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "One Click Creation of an AWS Lambda Trigger",
        "answer": "AWS IoT 1-Click",
        "distractors": [
          "Amazon EC2",
          "AWS Lake Formation",
          "AWS Batch"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Analytics for IoT Devices",
        "answer": "AWS IoT Analytics",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS RoboMaker",
          "Amazon Comprehend",
          "Amazon DocumentDB (with MongoDB compatibility)"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Cloud Programmable Dash Button",
        "answer": "AWS IoT Button",
        "distractors": [
          "TensorFlow on AWS",
          "AWS Data Exchange",
          "Amazon Kendra"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Security Management for IoT Devices",
        "answer": "AWS IoT Device Defender",
        "distractors": [
          "Amazon Elastic Container Registry",
          "AWS Transit Gateway",
          "AWS RoboMaker"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Onboard, Organize, and Remotely Manage IoT Devices",
        "answer": "AWS IoT Device Management",
        "distractors": [
          "Amazon FreeRTOS",
          "Amazon Quantum Ledger Database (QLDB)",
          "AWS License Manager"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "IoT event detection and response",
        "answer": "AWS IoT Events",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS Elemental MediaTailor",
          "AWS Serverless Application Repository",
          "AWS Elastic Beanstalk"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "IoT data collector and interpreter",
        "answer": "AWS IoT SiteWise",
        "distractors": [
          "Elastic Load Balancing",
          "AWS Console Mobile Application",
          "Apache MXNet on AWS"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Easily connect devices and web services",
        "answer": "AWS IoT Things Graph",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS License Manager",
          "AWS Elemental MediaConnect",
          "AWS CloudFormation"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Curated catalog of AWS-compatible IoT hardware",
        "answer": "AWS Partner Device Catalog",
        "distractors": [
          "Amazon Macie",
          "AWS OpsWorks",
          "AWS Snow Family"
        ]
      }
    ],
    "machine_learning": [
      {
        "question": "Build, Train, and Deploy Machine Learning Models at Scale",
        "answer": "Amazon SageMaker",
        "distractors": [
          "Amazon Timestream",
          "AWS Single Sign-On",
          "Apache MXNet on AWS"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Easily implement human review of ML predictions",
        "answer": "Amazon Augmented AI",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS Transfer for SFTP",
          "AWS RoboMaker",
          "Amazon Elastic Transcoder"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Automate code reviews and identify expensive lines of code",
        "answer": "Amazon CodeGuru",
        "distractors": [
          "Amazon WorkMail",
          "Amazon Athena",
          "Amazon Quantum Ledger Database (QLDB)"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Discover Insights and Relationships in Text",
        "answer": "Amazon Comprehend",
        "distractors": [
          "Savings Plans",
          "AWS IoT Analytics",
          "AWS Auto Scaling"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Deep learning inference acceleration",
        "answer": "Amazon Elastic Inference",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS Elemental MediaStore",
          "Amazon EMR",
          "Amazon Elastic Kubernetes Service"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Increase forecast accuracy using machine learning",
        "answer": "Amazon Forecast",
        "distractors": [
          "Amazon Macie",
          "AWS Config",
          "AWS Elemental MediaConnect"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Detect more online fraud faster",
        "answer": "Amazon Fraud Detector",
        "distractors": [
          "Amazon Simple Notification Service (SNS)",
          "AWS Budgets",
          "AWS Cloud9"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Reinvent enterprise search with ML",
        "answer": "Amazon Kendra",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS IoT Button",
          "TensorFlow on AWS",
          "AWS Glue"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Build Voice and Text Chatbots",
        "answer": "Amazon Lex",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS X-Ray",
          "Amazon Timestream",
          "Amazon Cognito"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Build real-time recommendations into your applications",
        "answer": "Amazon Personalize",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS CloudFormation",
          "Amazon GuardDuty",
          "AWS Transfer for SFTP"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Turn Text into Lifelike Speech",
        "answer": "Amazon Polly",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS Glue",
          "TensorFlow on AWS",
          "Amazon CloudWatch"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Analyze Image and Video",
        "answer": "Amazon Rekognition",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS Compute Optimizer",
          "Amazon EMR",
          "Amazon WorkSpaces"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Build accurate ML training datasets",
        "answer": "Amazon SageMaker Ground Truth",
        "distractors": [
          "Savings Plans",
          "AWS Cloud Development Kit (CDK)",
          "AWS IoT Core"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Extract text and data from documents",
        "answer": "Amazon Textract",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS Chatbot",
          "AWS DeepLens",
          "AWS CodeDeploy"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Natural and Fluent Language Translation",
        "answer": "Amazon Translate",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS Artifact",
          "AWS PrivateLink",
          "AWS Command Line Interface"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Automatic Speech Recognition",
        "answer": "Amazon Transcribe",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS CloudHSM",
          "Amazon OpenSearch Service",
          "Amazon Redshift"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Quickly Start Deep Learning on EC2",
        "answer": "AWS Deep Learning AMIs",
        "distractors": [
          "Amazon Simple Storage Service (S3)",
          "AWS CloudFormation",
          "AWS Control Tower"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Docker images for deep learning",
        "answer": "AWS Deep Learning Containers",
        "distractors": [
          "CloudEndure Disaster Recovery",
          "Amazon AppStream 2.0",
          "AWS DeepLens"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "ML enabled musical keyboard",
        "answer": "AWS DeepComposer",
        "distractors": [
          "Amazon Transcribe",
          "AWS Direct Connect",
          "Amazon Kendra"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Deep Learning Enabled Video Camera",
        "answer": "AWS DeepLens",
        "distractors": [
          "Amazon Athena",
          "AWS Inferentia2",
          "AWS Tools and SDKs"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Autonomous 1/18th scale race car, driven by ML",
        "answer": "AWS DeepRacer",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS Identity & Access Management",
          "AWS Console Mobile Application",
          "Apache MXNet on AWS"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Machine learning inference chip",
        "answer": "AWS Inferentia2",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS Glue",
          "AWS Backup",
          "AWS Lake Formation"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Scalable, High-performance Deep Learning",
        "answer": "Apache MXNet on AWS",
        "distractors": [
          "Amazon Braket",
          "Amazon Lightsail",
          "Amazon ElastiCache"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Open-source Machine Intelligence Library",
        "answer": "TensorFlow on AWS",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS Cloud Development Kit (CDK)",
          "Reserved Instance Reporting",
          "AWS Amplify"
        ]
      }
    ],
    "management_and_governance": [
      {
        "question": "Monitor Resources and Applications",
        "answer": "Amazon CloudWatch",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS Inferentia2",
          "AWS Ground Station",
          "AWS Config"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Scale Multiple Resources to Meet Demand",
        "answer": "AWS Auto Scaling",
        "distractors": [
          "Amazon Fraud Detector",
          "Elastic Load Balancing",
          "AWS Application Discovery Service"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "ChatOps for AWS",
        "answer": "AWS Chatbot",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS Direct Connect",
          "AWS X-Ray",
          "AWS IoT Events"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Create and Manage Resources with Templates",
        "answer": "AWS CloudFormation",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS Snow Family",
          "AWS Direct Connect",
          "Amazon Managed Streaming for Apache Kafka"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Track User Activity and API Usage",
        "answer": "AWS CloudTrail",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS RoboMaker",
          "AWS Transit Gateway",
          "AWS Compute Optimizer"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Unified tool to manage AWS services",
        "answer": "AWS Command Line Interface",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS Storage Gateway",
          "AWS Cloud9",
          "AWS Elemental Appliances & Software"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Identify optimal AWS Compute resources",
        "answer": "AWS Compute Optimizer",
        "distractors": [
          "Amazon WorkDocs",
          "Amazon OpenSearch Service",
          "Amazon VPC"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Track Resource Inventory and Changes",
        "answer": "AWS Config",
        "distractors": [
          "Amazon Fraud Detector",
          "AWS Auto Scaling",
          "AWS Command Line Interface"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Set up and govern a secure, compliant, multi-account environment",
        "answer": "AWS Control Tower",
        "distractors": [
          "Amazon Sumerian",
          "AWS Shield",
          "AWS PrivateLink"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Access resources on the go",
        "answer": "AWS Console Mobile Application",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS Compute Optimizer",
          "AWS Elemental MediaLive",
          "AWS Key Management Service"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Track, manage, and control licenses",
        "answer": "AWS License Manager",
        "distractors": [
          "Amazon Elastic Transcoder",
          "AWS Config",
          "AWS Cloud Map"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Web-based user interface",
        "answer": "AWS Management Console",
        "distractors": [
          "Amazon AppStream 2.0",
          "AWS Direct Connect",
          "Amazon EMR"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Infrastructure operations management for AWS",
        "answer": "AWS Managed Services",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS Compute Optimizer",
          "Amazon SageMaker Ground Truth",
          "Amazon Quantum Ledger Database (QLDB)"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Automate Operations with Chef and Puppet",
        "answer": "AWS OpsWorks",
        "distractors": [
          "Amazon Detective",
          "Amazon Sumerian",
          "AWS X-Ray"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Central governance and management across AWS accounts",
        "answer": "AWS Organizations",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS IoT Core",
          "AWS Compute Optimizer",
          "AWS Console Mobile Application"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Personalized View of AWS Service Health",
        "answer": "AWS Personal Health Dashboard",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS Lambda",
          "AWS Step Functions",
          "AWS Device Farm"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Create and Use Standardized Products",
        "answer": "AWS Service Catalog",
        "distractors": [
          "Amazon Braket",
          "Amazon Athena",
          "Amazon CodeGuru"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Gain Operational Insights and Take Action",
        "answer": "AWS Systems Manager",
        "distractors": [
          "Amazon Elastic Transcoder",
          "Amazon CloudSearch",
          "AWS Glue"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Optimize Performance and Security",
        "answer": "AWS Trusted Advisor",
        "distractors": [
          "Amazon Simple Notification Service (SNS)",
          "AWS Elemental Appliances & Software",
          "AWS Command Line Interface"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Review and improve your workloads",
        "answer": "AWS Well-Architected Tool",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS Service Catalog",
          "AWS Auto Scaling",
          "AWS Ground Station"
        ]
      }
    ],
    "media_services": [
      {
        "question": "Easy-to-use Scalable Media Transcoding",
        "answer": "Amazon Elastic Transcoder",
        "distractors": [
          "Amazon Fraud Detector",
          "AWS IoT Analytics",
          "AWS OpsWorks"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Process and Analyze Video Streams",
        "answer": "Amazon Kinesis Video Streams",
        "distractors": [
          "Amazon RDS on VMware",
          "Amazon Corretto",
          "AWS Tools and SDKs"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Reliable and secure live video transport",
        "answer": "AWS Elemental MediaConnect",
        "distractors": [
          "Elastic Load Balancing",
          "Amazon Quantum Ledger Database (QLDB)",
          "AWS Tools and SDKs"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Convert File-based Video Content",
        "answer": "AWS Elemental MediaConvert",
        "distractors": [
          "Amazon SageMaker Ground Truth",
          "Apache MXNet on AWS",
          "Amazon Timestream"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Convert Live Video Content",
        "answer": "AWS Elemental MediaLive",
        "distractors": [
          "Amazon FreeRTOS",
          "AWS Device Farm",
          "Amazon Translate"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Video Origination and Packaging",
        "answer": "AWS Elemental MediaPackage",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS Config",
          "TensorFlow on AWS",
          "AWS CloudTrail"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Media Storage and Simple HTTP Origin",
        "answer": "AWS Elemental MediaStore",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS IoT Core",
          "Amazon RDS on VMware",
          "AWS Deep Learning Containers"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Video Personalization and Monetization",
        "answer": "AWS Elemental MediaTailor",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS CodeStar",
          "AWS Cloud Development Kit (CDK)",
          "Amazon Corretto"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "On-premises media solutions",
        "answer": "AWS Elemental Appliances & Software",
        "distractors": [
          "Amazon Aurora",
          "Amazon Simple Email Service (SES)",
          "Amazon Elastic Container Service"
        ]
      }
    ],
    "migration_and_transfer": [
      {
        "question": "Track Migrations from a Single Place",
        "answer": "AWS Migration Hub",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS Personal Health Dashboard",
          "AWS Data Exchange",
          "AWS Control Tower"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Discover On-Premises Applications to Streamline Migration",
        "answer": "AWS Application Discovery Service",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS IoT Analytics",
          "AWS Wavelength",
          "AWS Cost Explorer"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Migrate Databases with Minimal Downtime",
        "answer": "AWS Database Migration Service",
        "distractors": [
          "Amazon Athena",
          "Amazon RDS",
          "Amazon OpenSearch Service"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Simple, fast, online data transfer",
        "answer": "AWS DataSync",
        "distractors": [
          "Amazon OpenSearch Service",
          "AWS CodeBuild",
          "Amazon CodeGuru"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Migrate On-Premises Servers to AWS",
        "answer": "AWS Application Migration Service",
        "distractors": [
          "Contact Lens for Amazon Connect",
          "AWS App Mesh",
          "Amazon Connect"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Physical devices to migrate data into and out of AWS",
        "answer": "AWS Snow Family",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS DeepLens",
          "Amazon Timestream",
          "Amazon Elastic Container Service"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Managed file transfer service (SFTP/FTPS/FTP)",
        "answer": "AWS Transfer Family",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS Cloud9",
          "Amazon Elastic Inference",
          "Amazon SageMaker Ground Truth"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Automate your mass migration to AWS",
        "answer": "CloudEndure Migration",
        "distractors": [
          "Amazon Elastic Kubernetes Service",
          "AWS Lake Formation",
          "Amazon Cognito"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Mainframe migration and modernization service",
        "answer": "AWS Mainframe Modernization",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS Database Migration Service",
          "AWS App2Container",
          "AWS Server Migration Service"
        ]
      }
    ],
    "mobile": [
      {
        "question": "Build and deploy mobile and web applications",
        "answer": "AWS Amplify",
        "distractors": [
          "Amazon Aurora",
          "Amazon Chime",
          "Reserved Instance Reporting"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Build, Deploy, and Manage APIs",
        "answer": "Amazon API Gateway",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS Device Farm",
          "Amazon Simple Email Service (SES)",
          "AWS Lake Formation"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Personalized User Engagement Across Channels",
        "answer": "Amazon Pinpoint",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS DeepLens",
          "AWS CodeBuild",
          "AWS Data Exchange"
        ]
      },

      {
        "question": "Test Android, iOS, and web apps on real devices in the AWS cloud",
        "answer": "AWS Device Farm",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS Control Tower",
          "Amazon Corretto",
          "Amazon Quantum Ledger Database (QLDB)"
        ]
      }
    ],
    "networking_and_content_delivery": [
      {
        "question": "Isolated Cloud Resources",
        "answer": "Amazon VPC",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS Single Sign-On",
          "Amazon CloudWatch",
          "AWS Config"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Layer 4 load balancer that directs TCP traffic",
        "answer": "Network Load Balancer",
        "distractors": [
          "Application Load Balancer",
          "Classic Load Balancer",
          "Gateway Load Balancer"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Build, Deploy, and Manage APIs",
        "answer": "Amazon API Gateway",
        "distractors": [
          "Amazon EventBridge",
          "Amazon OpenSearch Service",
          "AWS Certificate Manager"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Global Content Delivery Network",
        "answer": "Amazon CloudFront",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS Tools and SDKs",
          "AWS Device Farm",
          "AWS Personal Health Dashboard"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Scalable Domain Name System",
        "answer": "Amazon Route 53",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS Config",
          "Amazon Elastic Container Service",
          "AWS CodeDeploy"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Securely Access Services Hosted on AWS",
        "answer": "AWS PrivateLink",
        "distractors": [
          "Amazon WorkMail",
          "Amazon WorkSpaces",
          "AWS App Mesh"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Monitor and control microservices",
        "answer": "AWS App Mesh",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS Batch",
          "Amazon Inspector",
          "AWS CloudTrail"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Application resource registry for microservices",
        "answer": "AWS Cloud Map",
        "distractors": [
          "Amazon Chime",
          "Amazon Quantum Ledger Database (QLDB)",
          "AWS IoT Events"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Dedicated Network Connection to AWS",
        "answer": "AWS Direct Connect",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS Amplify",
          "Amazon Sumerian",
          "AWS IoT Button"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Managed site-to-site VPN",
        "answer": "AWS Site-to-Site VPN",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS Client VPN",
          "AWS Direct Connect",
          "AWS Transit Gateway"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Improve application availability and performance",
        "answer": "AWS Global Accelerator",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS Service Catalog",
          "AWS Data Exchange",
          "AWS CodeStar"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Easily scale VPC and account connections",
        "answer": "AWS Transit Gateway",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS Device Farm",
          "Amazon Aurora",
          "AWS IoT Core"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Distribute incoming traffic across multiple targets",
        "answer": "Elastic Load Balancing",
        "distractors": [
          "Amazon Route 53",
          "Amazon Kinesis",
          "AWS Deep Learning Containers"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Service networking for private connectivity",
        "answer": "Amazon VPC Lattice",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS App Mesh",
          "AWS PrivateLink",
          "AWS Transit Gateway"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Managed private 5G network service",
        "answer": "AWS Private 5G",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS Wavelength",
          "AWS Direct Connect",
          "AWS IoT Core"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Managed network firewall for VPCs",
        "answer": "AWS Network Firewall",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS WAF",
          "AWS Shield",
          "AWS Transit Gateway"
        ]
      }
    ],
    "quantum_technologies": [
      {
        "question": "Explore and experiment with quantum computing",
        "answer": "Amazon Braket",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS Data Pipeline",
          "AWS DeepLens",
          "AWS Console Mobile Application"
        ]
      }
    ],
    "satellite": [
      {
        "question": "Fully managed ground station as a service",
        "answer": "AWS Ground Station",
        "distractors": [
          "Amazon EC2 Auto Scaling",
          "Amazon EMR",
          "Amazon EMR"
        ]
      }
    ],
    "robotics": [
      {
        "question": "Develop, test, and deploy robotics applications",
        "answer": "AWS RoboMaker",
        "distractors": [
          "Amazon Athena",
          "Amazon Athena",
          "Amazon CloudSearch"
        ]
      }
    ],

    "security_and_compliance": [
      {
        "question": "Manage User Access and Encryption Keys",
        "answer": "AWS Identity & Access Management",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS Elastic Beanstalk",
          "Amazon EMR",
          "Amazon DynamoDB"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Identity Management for your Apps",
        "answer": "Amazon Cognito",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS IoT Device Management",
          "Amazon Detective",
          "Amazon FSx for Lustre"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Investigate potential security issues",
        "answer": "Amazon Detective",
        "distractors": [
          "Amazon Forecast",
          "Amazon Elastic Kubernetes Service",
          "AWS Cost and Usage Report"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Managed Threat Detection Service",
        "answer": "Amazon GuardDuty",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS AppSync",
          "AWS Data Pipeline",
          "Amazon EMR"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Analyze Application Security",
        "answer": "Amazon Inspector",
        "distractors": [
          "CloudEndure Migration",
          "AWS CodeStar",
          "Amazon Fraud Detector"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Discover, Classify, and Protect your Data",
        "answer": "Amazon Macie",
        "distractors": [
          "Amazon Cognito",
          "AWS DeepLens",
          "Amazon Elastic Container Service"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "On-demand access to AWS compliance reports",
        "answer": "AWS Artifact",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS IoT SiteWise",
          "Amazon Athena",
          "Amazon WorkMail"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Provision, Manage, and Deploy SSL/TLS Certificates",
        "answer": "AWS Certificate Manager",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS Transit Gateway",
          "AWS Firewall Manager",
          "AWS Data Exchange"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Hardware-based Key Storage for Regulatory Compliance",
        "answer": "AWS CloudHSM",
        "distractors": [
          "Amazon FSx for Windows File Server",
          "Amazon OpenSearch Service",
          "Amazon Timestream"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Host and Manage Active Directory",
        "answer": "AWS Directory Service",
        "distractors": [
          "Amazon Elastic Container Registry",
          "AWS Security Hub",
          "AWS Elemental MediaConnect"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Central Management of Firewall Rules",
        "answer": "AWS Firewall Manager",
        "distractors": [
          "Amazon RDS on VMware",
          "AWS Systems Manager",
          "AWS Data Pipeline"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Managed Creation and Control of Encryption Keys",
        "answer": "AWS Key Management Service",
        "distractors": [
          "Amazon Athena",
          "AWS Cloud Development Kit (CDK)",
          "AWS Managed Services"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Simple, secure service to share AWS resources",
        "answer": "AWS Resource Access Manager",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS Greengrass",
          "CloudEndure Migration",
          "Amazon Lumberyard"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Rotate, Manage, and Retrieve Secrets",
        "answer": "AWS Secrets Manager",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS Storage Gateway",
          "Amazon Elastic Container Registry",
          "Amazon EC2 Auto Scaling"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Unified security and compliance center",
        "answer": "AWS Security Hub",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS IoT Analytics",
          "Amazon Corretto",
          "Amazon CloudSearch"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "DDoS Protection",
        "answer": "AWS Shield",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS Transit Gateway",
          "Amazon Route 53",
          "AWS Management Console"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Cloud Single Sign-On (SSO) Service",
        "answer": "AWS Single Sign-On",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS Elemental MediaConnect",
          "Amazon QuickSight",
          "Amazon Redshift"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Filter Malicious Web Traffic",
        "answer": "AWS WAF",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS Directory Service",
          "Apache MXNet on AWS",
          "AWS Amplify"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Zero-trust application access service",
        "answer": "AWS Verified Access",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS WAF",
          "AWS PrivateLink",
          "Amazon Cognito"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Secure end-to-end encrypted messaging (successor to Wickr)",
        "answer": "AWS End User Messaging",
        "distractors": [
          "Amazon Chime",
          "Amazon SNS",
          "AWS AppSync"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Centralized security data lake service",
        "answer": "Amazon Security Lake",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS Security Hub",
          "Amazon GuardDuty",
          "Amazon Detective"
        ]
      }
    ],
    "storage": [
      {
        "question": "Scalable Storage in the Cloud",
        "answer": "Amazon Simple Storage Service (S3)",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS App Mesh",
          "AWS CodePipeline",
          "Amazon RDS on VMware"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "EC2 block storage volumes",
        "answer": "Amazon Elastic Block Store (EBS)",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS Control Tower",
          "AWS Elemental MediaLive",
          "AWS DeepRacer"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Fully managed file system for EC2",
        "answer": "Amazon Elastic File System (EFS)",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS Ground Station",
          "AWS Control Tower",
          "AWS Elemental MediaTailor"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "High-performance file system integrated with S3",
        "answer": "Amazon FSx for Lustre",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS IoT Analytics",
          "AWS Cloud9",
          "AWS Artifact"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Fully managed Windows native file system",
        "answer": "Amazon FSx for Windows File Server",
        "distractors": [
          "Amazon Macie",
          "Amazon Rekognition",
          "Amazon Personalize"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Low-cost Archive Storage in the Cloud",
        "answer": "Amazon S3 Glacier",
        "distractors": [
          "Amazon Elastic File System (EFS)",
          "Amazon SageMaker",
          "Amazon Quantum Ledger Database (QLDB)"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Centralized backup across AWS services",
        "answer": "AWS Backup",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS Well-Architected Tool",
          "AWS CodeBuild",
          "AWS CodeCommit"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Physical devices to migrate data into and out of AWS",
        "answer": "AWS Snow Family",
        "distractors": [
          "Amazon Elastic Transcoder",
          "AWS Auto Scaling",
          "AWS Cloud Development Kit (CDK)"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Hybrid Storage Integration",
        "answer": "AWS Storage Gateway",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS DeepComposer",
          "AWS Outposts",
          "AWS Organizations"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Highly automated disaster recovery",
        "answer": "CloudEndure Disaster Recovery",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS Identity & Access Management",
          "Amazon Route 53",
          "Amazon API Gateway"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Fully managed Apache Kafka service",
        "answer": "Amazon Managed Streaming for Apache Kafka",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS Ground Station",
          "AWS Greengrass",
          "AWS Compute Optimizer"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Fast, Simple, Cost-effective Data Warehousing",
        "answer": "Amazon Redshift",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS Data Exchange",
          "Amazon Macie",
          "AWS Management Console"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Fast Business Analytics Service",
        "answer": "Amazon QuickSight",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS Inferentia2",
          "Amazon EMR",
          "AWS IoT Events"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Find, subscribe to, and use third-party data in the cloud",
        "answer": "AWS Data Exchange",
        "distractors": [
          "Amazon RDS on VMware",
          "AWS Glue",
          "Amazon Redshift"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Orchestration Service for Periodic, Data-driven Workflows",
        "answer": "AWS Data Pipeline",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS Batch",
          "Amazon Aurora",
          "Amazon Simple Email Service (SES)"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Prepare and Load Data",
        "answer": "AWS Glue",
        "distractors": [
          "Amazon Athena",
          "Amazon Kinesis Video Streams",
          "AWS Lambda"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Build a secure data lake in days",
        "answer": "AWS Lake Formation",
        "distractors": [
          "Amazon AppStream 2.0",
          "AWS Secrets Manager",
          "Amazon WorkDocs"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Coordinate Distributed Applications",
        "answer": "AWS Step Functions",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS CodeDeploy",
          "AWS Cloud Development Kit (CDK)",
          "AWS IoT Device Defender"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Serverless event bus for SaaS apps & AWS services",
        "answer": "Amazon EventBridge",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS Elemental MediaTailor",
          "AWS CodeBuild",
          "Amazon WorkDocs"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Managed Message Broker for ActiveMQ",
        "answer": "Amazon MQ",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS Elemental MediaTailor",
          "AWS Serverless Application Repository",
          "Amazon OpenSearch Service"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Pub/Sub, Mobile Push and SMS",
        "answer": "Amazon Simple Notification Service (SNS)",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS Cloud9",
          "Amazon Macie",
          "Amazon Redshift"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Managed Message Queues",
        "answer": "Amazon Simple Queue Service (SQS)",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS Single Sign-On",
          "Amazon Managed Blockchain",
          "Amazon Lumberyard"
        ]
      }
      
    ],
    "messaging_and_eventing": [
      {
        "question": "Serverless event bus for SaaS apps & AWS services",
        "answer": "Amazon EventBridge",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS Elemental MediaTailor",
          "AWS CodeBuild",
          "Amazon WorkDocs"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Pub/Sub, Mobile Push and SMS",
        "answer": "Amazon Simple Notification Service (SNS)",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS Cloud9",
          "Amazon Macie",
          "Amazon Redshift"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Managed Message Queues",
        "answer": "Amazon Simple Queue Service (SQS)",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS Single Sign-On",
          "Amazon Managed Blockchain",
          "Amazon Lumberyard"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Managed Message Broker for ActiveMQ",
        "answer": "Amazon MQ",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS Elemental MediaTailor",
          "AWS Serverless Application Repository",
          "Amazon OpenSearch Service"
        ]
      }
    ],
    "edge_and_hybrid": [
      {
        "question": "Deliver ultra-low latency edge computing for 5G devices",
        "answer": "AWS Wavelength",
        "distractors": [
          "Amazon Elastic Inference",
          "Amazon Managed Streaming for Apache Kafka",
          "Amazon Macie"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Run AWS infrastructure in your data center",
        "answer": "AWS Outposts",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS Direct Connect",
          "AWS Snow Family",
          "Amazon EC2"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Extend AWS infrastructure to selected metro areas",
        "answer": "AWS Local Zones",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS Outposts",
          "Amazon EC2",
          "AWS Wavelength"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Physical devices to migrate data into and out of AWS",
        "answer": "AWS Snow Family",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS Identity & Access Management",
          "Amazon Route 53",
          "Amazon API Gateway"
        ]
      }
    ],
    "healthcare_and_life_sciences": [
      {
        "question": "Centralized repository for healthcare data and analytics",
        "answer": "Amazon HealthLake",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS HealthImaging",
          "Amazon Omics",
          "Amazon S3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Transcribe medical speech to text with specialized models",
        "answer": "Amazon Transcribe Medical",
        "distractors": [
          "Amazon Transcribe",
          "Amazon Comprehend Medical",
          "Amazon Translate"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Extract clinical concepts from medical text",
        "answer": "Amazon Comprehend Medical",
        "distractors": [
          "Amazon Comprehend",
          "AWS HealthScribe",
          "Amazon Textract"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "AI-powered medical image analysis",
        "answer": "AWS HealthImaging",
        "distractors": [
          "Amazon Comprehend Medical",
          "Amazon Transcribe Medical",
          "AWS HealthScribe"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Managed service for genomic analysis and storage",
        "answer": "Amazon Omics",
        "distractors": [
          "Amazon HealthLake",
          "AWS Glue",
          "Amazon Redshift"
        ]
      }
    ],
    "acronyms": [
      {
        "question": "AWS",
        "answer": "Amazon Web Services ",
        "distractors": [
          "Adapter Workflow Socket ",
          "Array Workflow Security ",
          "Authentication Web Service "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Amazon ES",
        "answer": "Amazon OpenSearch Service ",
        "distractors": [
          "Automation Encryption Secure ",
          "Access Encryption Services ",
          "Access Extensions System "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "AMI",
        "answer": "Amazon Machine Image ",
        "distractors": [
          "Array Module Interface ",
          "Application Markup Inter-Domain ",
          "Attack MapReduce Image "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "API",
        "answer": "Application Programming Interface ",
        "distractors": [
          "Analytics Private Image ",
          "Automation Program Interface ",
          "Array Platform Independent "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "AI",
        "answer": "Artificial Intelligence ",
        "distractors": [
          "Adapter Independent ",
          "Address Indication ",
          "Amazon Image "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "ACL",
        "answer": "Access Control List ",
        "distractors": [
          "Authentication Capacity Line ",
          "Amazon Check Live ",
          "Amazon Compute Layer "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "ALB",
        "answer": "Application Load Balancer ",
        "distractors": [
          "Adapter Load Balancer ",
          "Amazon License Balancer ",
          "Attack Load Balancing "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "ARN",
        "answer": "Amazon Resource Name ",
        "distractors": [
          "Amazon Redundancy Network ",
          "Assertion Resource Notation ",
          "Authority Resource Network "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "AZ",
        "answer": "Availability Zone ",
        "distractors": [
          "Agreement Zone ",
          "Assertion Zone ",
          "Assertion Zone "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "ACM",
        "answer": "AWS Certificate Management ",
        "distractors": [
          "Amazon Client Machine ",
          "Access Container Machine ",
          "Automation Control Machine "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "ASG",
        "answer": "Auto Scaling Group ",
        "distractors": [
          "Amazon Second Gateway ",
          "Agreement System Group ",
          "Access System Group "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "AES",
        "answer": "Advanced Encryption Standard",
        "distractors": [
          "Adapter Extensions Services ",
          "Adapter Encryption Storage ",
          "Access Extensions Service "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "ADFS",
        "answer": "Active Directory Federation Service ",
        "distractors": [
          "Assertion Database File Store ",
          "Attack Directory First Service ",
          "Access Disk File S3 "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "AVX",
        "answer": "Advanced Vector Extensions (AVX/AVX-512)",
        "distractors": [
          "Adapter Virtual Encryption ",
          "Application Virtual Encryption ",
          "Authority Virtual Encryption "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "BYOL",
        "answer": "Bring Your Own License ",
        "distractors": [
          "Block Your Of Load ",
          "Balancer Your Own List ",
          "Balancer Your Of List "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "CDN",
        "answer": "Content Delivery Network ",
        "distractors": [
          "Class Data Name ",
          "Compute Denial Network ",
          "Container Desktop Network "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "CRC",
        "answer": "Cyclic Redundancy Check ",
        "distractors": [
          "Certificate Resource Compute ",
          "Compute Routing Control ",
          "Compute Resource Cloud "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "CLI",
        "answer": "Command Line Interface ",
        "distractors": [
          "Container Layer Initiative ",
          "Cloud List Integration/Continuous ",
          "Compute Layer Indication "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "CIDR",
        "answer": "Classless Inter-Domain Routing ",
        "distractors": [
          "Container Interface Redundancy ",
          "Capacity IP Resource ",
          "Compute Integration/Continuous Reliable "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "CORS",
        "answer": "Cross Origin Resource Sharing ",
        "distractors": [
          "Container Object Resource System ",
          "Container Origin Resource Service ",
          "Check Own Registry Server "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "CRR",
        "answer": "Cross Region Replication ",
        "distractors": [
          "Control Region Resource ",
          "Capacity Repository Repository ",
          "Control Replication Replication "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "CI/CD",
        "answer": "Continuous Integration/Continuous Deployment ",
        "distractors": [
          "Control Interface Datagrams ",
          "Computer Interface Denial ",
          "Check Inter-Domain Disk "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "DMS",
        "answer": "Database Migration Service ",
        "distractors": [
          "Directory Machine Sign-On ",
          "Delivery Memory S3 ",
          "Directory Machine Scaling "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "DNS",
        "answer": "Domain Name System ",
        "distractors": [
          "Database Network Socket ",
          "Datagrams Network Storage ",
          "Directory Name Service "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "DDoS",
        "answer": "Distributed Denial of Service ",
        "distractors": [
          "Design Data S3 ",
          "Data Design Second ",
          "Deployment Disk Storage "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "DoS",
        "answer": "Denial of Service ",
        "distractors": [
          "Denial Service ",
          "Development Second ",
          "Deployment Storage "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "DaaS",
        "answer": "Desktop as-a-Service ",
        "distractors": [
          "Design as-a-Service ",
          "Disk as-a-Service ",
          "Disk as-a-Service "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "EC2",
        "answer": "Elastic Compute Cloud ",
        "distractors": [
          "Encryption Control Cloud ",
          "Email Cloud Client ",
          "Email Compute Control "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "ECS",
        "answer": "EC2 Container Service ",
        "distractors": [
          "Email Control Security ",
          "Encryption Container Side ",
          "Encryption Capacity System "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "ECR",
        "answer": "Elastic Container Registry ",
        "distractors": [
          "Encryption Certificate Resource ",
          "Emulator Check Redundancy ",
          "Emulator Cloud Reliable "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "EFS",
        "answer": "Elastic File System ",
        "distractors": [
          "Extensions Firewall Service ",
          "Encryption Fabric System ",
          "Encryption First System "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "EI",
        "answer": "Elastic Inference ",
        "distractors": [
          "Encryption Interface ",
          "Express Interface ",
          "Encryption Inference "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "ENA",
        "answer": "Elastic Network Adapter ",
        "distractors": [
          "Encryption Network Array ",
          "Encryption Network Access ",
          "Express Name Access "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "EKS",
        "answer": "Elastic Kubernetes Service ",
        "distractors": [
          "Extensions Kit Service ",
          "Encryption Kubernetes Service ",
          "Encryption Kit Service "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "EBS",
        "answer": "Elastic Block Store ",
        "distractors": [
          "Express Balancer Scaling ",
          "Encryption Balancing Service ",
          "Encryption Balancer System "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "EMR",
        "answer": "Elastic MapReduce ",
        "distractors": [
          "Encryption Machine ",
          "Encryption Migration ",
          "Express MapReduce "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "ELB",
        "answer": "Elastic Load Balancing ",
        "distractors": [
          "Encryption Load Balancer ",
          "Encryption License Balancer ",
          "Extensions Layer Balancer "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "EFA",
        "answer": "Elastic Fabric Adapter ",
        "distractors": [
          "Email Fabric Address ",
          "Emulator Firewall Analytics ",
          "Express First Adapter "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "EIP",
        "answer": "Elastic IP ",
        "distractors": [
          "Elastic Instance Provisioning",
          "Enhanced IP Protocol",
          "External Internet Pathway"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "EDA",
        "answer": "Electronic Design Automation ",
        "distractors": [
          "Express Data Attack ",
          "Emulator Design Agreement ",
          "Extensions Design Access "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "ENI",
        "answer": "Elastic Network Interface ",
        "distractors": [
          "Encryption Network Integration/Continuous ",
          "Encryption Name Interface ",
          "Encryption Network Interface "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "ECU",
        "answer": "EC2 Compute Unit ",
        "distractors": [
          "Encryption Container Unit ",
          "Emulator Control Unit ",
          "Encryption Control Unit "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "FIFO",
        "answer": "First In First Out ",
        "distractors": [
          "Firewall First Object ",
          "File Federation Origin ",
          "First Fabric Out "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "FaaS",
        "answer": "Function as-a-Service ",
        "distractors": [
          "Federation as-a-Service ",
          "Federation as ",
          "Federation as "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "HPC",
        "answer": "High-Performance Compute ",
        "distractors": [
          "undefined Client ",
          "undefined Compute ",
          "undefined Compute "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "HVM",
        "answer": "Hardware Virtual Machine ",
        "distractors": [
          "undefined Virtual Memory ",
          "undefined Vector Management ",
          "undefined Virtual Machine "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "HTTP",
        "answer": "Hypertext Transfer Protocol ",
        "distractors": [
          "undefined Things Per ",
          "undefined Translation Programming ",
          "undefined Transfer Processing "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "HTTPS",
        "answer": "HTTP Secure ",
        "distractors": [
          "undefined System ",
          "undefined System ",
          "undefined Service "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "HDK",
        "answer": "Hardware Development Kit ",
        "distractors": [
          "undefined Directory Kit ",
          "undefined Disk Kit ",
          "undefined Development Kubernetes "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "IAM",
        "answer": "Identity & Access Management ",
        "distractors": [
          "Intelligence Array Management ",
          "Initiative Address Management ",
          "Image Automation Memory "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "iOT",
        "answer": "Internet Of Things ",
        "distractors": [
          "Integration/Continuous Transfer ",
          "Intelligence To ",
          "In Transaction "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "S3 IA",
        "answer": "S3 Infrequent Access ",
        "distractors": [
          "Intelligence Analytics ",
          "IP Access ",
          "Inference Area "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "iSCSI",
        "answer": "Internet Small Computer Storage Interface ",
        "distractors": [
          "Industry Side Control Standard Intelligence ",
          "Integration/Continuous Service Compute S3 IP ",
          "Independent Standard Certificate Security Integration/Continuous "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "IOPS",
        "answer": "Input/Output Operation Per Second ",
        "distractors": [
          "Independent Origin Processing Service ",
          "Image Origin Protocol Secure ",
          "Interface Of Processing S3 "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "IGW",
        "answer": "Internet Gateway ",
        "distractors": [
          "Instance Gateway ",
          "Industry Group ",
          "Instance Gateway "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "ICMP",
        "answer": "Internet Control Message Protocol ",
        "distractors": [
          "Industry Control Machine Parallel ",
          "In Container Memory Programming ",
          "Image Capacity Machine PCI "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "IP",
        "answer": "Internet Protocol ",
        "distractors": [
          "Image Protocol ",
          "Inter-Domain Protocol ",
          "Indication Private "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "IPSec",
        "answer": "Internet Protocol Security ",
        "distractors": [
          "Inference Programming Sharing ",
          "Industry Programming Security ",
          "Interface Per Server "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "IaaS",
        "answer": "Infrastructure-as-a-Service ",
        "distractors": [
          "Interface-as-a-Service",
          "Integration-as-a-Service",
          "Information-as-a-Service"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "JSON",
        "answer": "JavaScript Object Notation ",
        "distractors": [
          "undefined Operation Name ",
          "undefined Own Name ",
          "undefined Of Network "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "KMS",
        "answer": "Key Management Service ",
        "distractors": [
          "Kubernetes MapReduce Side ",
          "Kubernetes Markup Secure ",
          "Kit Machine System "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "KVM",
        "answer": "Kernel-based Virtual Machine ",
        "distractors": [
          "Kubernetes Virtual MapReduce ",
          "Kubernetes Vector Migration ",
          "Kit Virtual Machine "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "LB",
        "answer": "Load Balancer ",
        "distractors": [
          "Latency Balancer",
          "Load Buffer",
          "Link Bandwidth"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "LCU",
        "answer": "Load Balancer Capacity Unit ",
        "distractors": [
          "Line Balancer Control Unit ",
          "Layer Balancer Control Unit ",
          "List Balancing Cloud Unit "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "MFA",
        "answer": "Multi-Factor Authentication ",
        "distractors": [
          "Memory Authentication ",
          "Message Assertion ",
          "Markup Analytics "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "MSTSC",
        "answer": "Microsoft Terminal Service Client ",
        "distractors": [
          "Module Token Side Control ",
          "Machine Time Storage Check ",
          "Memory Translation Service Compute "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "MPP",
        "answer": "Massive Parallel Processing ",
        "distractors": [
          "MapReduce Programming Protocol ",
          "Management PCI Policies ",
          "Management Protocol Processing "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "MITM",
        "answer": "Man in the Middle Attack ",
        "distractors": [
          "Module the Memory Access ",
          "Markup the Markup Address ",
          "Module the Memory Assertion "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "MPLS",
        "answer": "Multi Protocol Label Switching ",
        "distractors": [
          "Machine Protocol Language Second ",
          "Machine Programming Line Second ",
          "Manager Protocol Level Service "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "MWAA",
        "answer": "Managed Workflows for Apache Airflow",
        "distractors": [
          "Managed Workflows for Apache Spark",
          "Amazon MWAA Service",
          "AWS Step Functions"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "NFS",
        "answer": "Network File System ",
        "distractors": [
          "Name Federation Server ",
          "Notification Fabric System ",
          "Network Fabric System "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "NS",
        "answer": "Name Server ",
        "distractors": [
          "Name Service ",
          "Name Services ",
          "Network Service "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "NAT",
        "answer": "Network Address Translation ",
        "distractors": [
          "Name Access Token ",
          "Name Amazon Translation ",
          "Network Authentication Translation "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "NVMe",
        "answer": "Non-Volatile Memory Express ",
        "distractors": [
          "Network Migration Encryption ",
          "Notification Memory Encryption ",
          "Network Markup Extensions "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "NLB",
        "answer": "Network Load Balancer ",
        "distractors": [
          "Node Location Broker ",
          "Native Logging Backend ",
          "Networked Logic Bridge "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "OLTP",
        "answer": "Online Transaction Processing ",
        "distractors": [
          "Of Transfer Per ",
          "Of Transfer Parallel ",
          "Of Translation Programming "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "OLAP",
        "answer": "Online Analytics Processing ",
        "distractors": [
          "Own Address Policies ",
          "Own Amazon Processing ",
          "Out Analysis Protocol "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "OCI",
        "answer": "Open Container Initiative ",
        "distractors": [
          "Own Control Interface ",
          "Out Control Interface ",
          "Own Client Integration/Continuous "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "PCI DSS",
        "answer": "Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard ",
        "distractors": [
          "Per Container Interface Data Security Storage ",
          "Platform Cloud Industry Design Storage Service ",
          "PCI Check Image Development Service Switching "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "PVM",
        "answer": "Para Virtual Machine ",
        "distractors": [
          "Private Virtual Memory ",
          "Private Virtual MapReduce ",
          "Private Virtual Machine "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "PV",
        "answer": "ParaVirtual ",
        "distractors": [
          "Partial Virtualization",
          "Provisioned Volume",
          "Private VLAN"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "PaaS",
        "answer": "Platform as a Service ",
        "distractors": [
          "Policies Shell ",
          "Processing Service ",
          "Protocol Service "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "RAID",
        "answer": "Redundant Array of Independent Disk ",
        "distractors": [
          "Replication Assertion Image Design ",
          "Repository Application Interface Design ",
          "Registry Area IP Design "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "RDS",
        "answer": "Relational Database Service ",
        "distractors": [
          "Region Design System ",
          "Redundancy Disk Service ",
          "Resource Database System "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "RRS",
        "answer": "Reduced Redundancy Storage ",
        "distractors": [
          "Registry Region Small ",
          "Resource Resource System ",
          "Resource Routing Service "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "RI",
        "answer": "Reserved Instance ",
        "distractors": [
          "Reliable Intelligence ",
          "Resource Image ",
          "Resource Interface "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "RAM",
        "answer": "Random-access Memory ",
        "distractors": [
          "Repository Message ",
          "Registry Message ",
          "Registry Machine "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "RIE",
        "answer": "Runtime Interface Emulator ",
        "distractors": [
          "Registry Infrastructure Express ",
          "Registry Initiative Express ",
          "Resource Interface Email "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "SSE",
        "answer": "Server Side Encryption ",
        "distractors": [
          "Service Service Encryption ",
          "Scaling Sign-On Encryption ",
          "Service Storage Express "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "S3",
        "answer": "Simple Storage Service ",
        "distractors": [
          "Service System Side ",
          "Services Security System ",
          "Service Service Service "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "S3 RTC",
        "answer": "S3 Replication Time Control ",
        "distractors": [
          "Routing Token Capacity ",
          "Routing Transfer Check ",
          "Redundancy Token Control "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "SRR",
        "answer": "Same Region Replication ",
        "distractors": [
          "Scaling Reliable Reliable ",
          "S3 Region Redundancy ",
          "System Registry Routing "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "SMS",
        "answer": "Server Migration Service ",
        "distractors": [
          "System Machine System ",
          "Server Machine Services ",
          "Scaling Management Service "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "SWF",
        "answer": "Simple Workflow Service ",
        "distractors": [
          "Security Workflow Side ",
          "Services Workflow Storage ",
          "Switching Web Security "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "SES",
        "answer": "Simple Email Service ",
        "distractors": [
          "Service Emulator Storage ",
          "Switching Express Secure ",
          "Service Encryption Service "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "SNS",
        "answer": "Simple Notification Service ",
        "distractors": [
          "Service Network Service ",
          "Storage Name System ",
          "System Notification Side "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "SQS",
        "answer": "Simple Queue Service ",
        "distractors": [
          "Second Queue Service ",
          "Second Queue Security ",
          "Side Queue Security "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "SES",
        "answer": "Simple Email Service ",
        "distractors": [
          "Scaling Email Storage ",
          "Sign-On Extensions Socket ",
          "Sign-On Email System "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "SLA",
        "answer": "Service Level Agreement ",
        "distractors": [
          "Standard License Authority ",
          "Scaling Language Address ",
          "Services Layer Agreement "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "SSL",
        "answer": "Secure Socket Layer ",
        "distractors": [
          "Secure Service Level ",
          "Service Service License ",
          "Storage Small List "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "SOA",
        "answer": "Start of Authority ",
        "distractors": [
          "Service Oriented Architecture ",
          "Secure Operations Administration ",
          "System Orchestration Automation "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "SDK",
        "answer": "Software Development Kit ",
        "distractors": [
          "Sign-On Database Kit ",
          "System Development Kubernetes ",
          "Services Database Kubernetes "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "SSH",
        "answer": "Secure Shell ",
        "distractors": [
          "Service Store ",
          "Service Standard ",
          "System Standard "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "SAR",
        "answer": "Serverless Application Repository ",
        "distractors": [
          "Service Address Redundancy ",
          "Sharing Adapter Redundancy ",
          "S3 Adapter Resource "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "SRD",
        "answer": "Scalable Reliable Datagrams ",
        "distractors": [
          "Storage Reliable Denial ",
          "Service Replication Data ",
          "Security Resource Database "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "SSO",
        "answer": "Single Sign-On ",
        "distractors": [
          "Single Service Object",
          "Secure Sign-On",
          "Shared Session Option"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "SAML",
        "answer": "Security Assertion Markup Language ",
        "distractors": [
          "Service Attack Machine Load ",
          "Service Authentication Migration Load ",
          "Service Adapter Management Layer "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "SaaS",
        "answer": "Software-as-a-Service ",
        "distractors": [
          "System-as-a-Service Architecture",
          "Storage-as-a-Service Application",
          "Solutions-as-a-Service Platform"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "SaaS",
        "answer": "Security-as-a-Service ",
        "distractors": [
          "Service ",
          "Service ",
          "Security "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "SCP",
        "answer": "Service Control Policies ",
        "distractors": [
          "Service Compute Per ",
          "Second Check Per ",
          "Sign-On Cloud Protocol "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "SCA",
        "answer": "Storage Class Analysis ",
        "distractors": [
          "Service Compute Analysis ",
          "Security Capacity Array ",
          "Store Compute Amazon "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "STS",
        "answer": "Security Token Service ",
        "distractors": [
          "Service Transfer Service ",
          "Store Token Service ",
          "Service Time Sharing "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "SNI",
        "answer": "Server Name Indication ",
        "distractors": [
          "Storage Name Image ",
          "Storage Name Intelligence ",
          "Sign-On Notification Instance "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "TTL",
        "answer": "Time To Live ",
        "distractors": [
          "Transaction Time Limit",
          "Transmission Timing Layer",
          "Token Time Lock"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "TLS",
        "answer": "Transport Layer Security ",
        "distractors": [
          "Terminal List Service ",
          "Transfer Line Security ",
          "Transfer Load Service "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "TPM",
        "answer": "Trusted Platform Module ",
        "distractors": [
          "Transfer Protocol Machine ",
          "Transfer Per Module ",
          "Terminal Protocol Management "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "TME",
        "answer": "Total Memory Encryption ",
        "distractors": [
          "Tape Management Encryption ",
          "Token Machine Emulator ",
          "Transfer Migration Email "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "TPM",
        "answer": "Technical Program Manager ",
        "distractors": [
          "Transfer Processing Migration ",
          "Transaction Programming Management ",
          "Translation Platform Markup "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "TPS",
        "answer": "Transaction Per Second ",
        "distractors": [
          "Transaction Processing Small ",
          "To Processing Shell ",
          "Time Processing Services "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "TCP",
        "answer": "Transmission Control Protocol ",
        "distractors": [
          "Time Compute Protocol ",
          "Translation Container Processing ",
          "Translation Control Per "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "VPC",
        "answer": "Virtual Private Cloud ",
        "distractors": [
          "Vector Policies Container ",
          "Virtual Processing Capacity ",
          "Virtual Protocol Control "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "VM",
        "answer": "Virtual Machine ",
        "distractors": [
          "Vector Management ",
          "Virtual Machine ",
          "Vector Machine "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "VTL",
        "answer": "Virtual Tape Library ",
        "distractors": [
          "Virtual Things Library ",
          "Virtual Translation Load ",
          "Vector To Library "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "VPN",
        "answer": "Virtual Private Network ",
        "distractors": [
          "Vector Parallel Network ",
          "Virtual Programming Name ",
          "Virtual PCI Network "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "VLAN",
        "answer": "Virtual Local Area Network ",
        "distractors": [
          "Virtual License Analytics Network ",
          "Vector Library Area Notation ",
          "Virtual Line Automation Name "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "VDI",
        "answer": "Virtual Desktop Infrastructure ",
        "distractors": [
          "Virtual Desktop Initiative ",
          "Virtual Directory Integration/Continuous ",
          "Vector Deployment Inference "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "VPG",
        "answer": "Virtual Private Gateway ",
        "distractors": [
          "Virtual Programming Group ",
          "Vector Protocol Gateway ",
          "Virtual Processing Group "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "WAF",
        "answer": "Web Application Firewall",
        "distractors": [
          "Web Assertion Federation ",
          "Workflow Automation File ",
          "Workflow Adapter File "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "CRC",
        "answer": "Cyclic Redundancy Check ",
        "distractors": [
          "Certificate Resource Compute ",
          "Compute Routing Control ",
          "Compute Resource Cloud "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "CLI",
        "answer": "Command Line Interface ",
        "distractors": [
          "Container Layer Initiative ",
          "Cloud List Integration/Continuous ",
          "Compute Layer Indication "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "CIDR",
        "answer": "Classless Inter-Domain Routing ",
        "distractors": [
          "Container Interface Redundancy ",
          "Capacity IP Resource ",
          "Compute Integration/Continuous Reliable "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "CORS",
        "answer": "Cross Origin Resource Sharing ",
        "distractors": [
          "Container Object Resource System ",
          "Container Origin Resource Service ",
          "Check Own Registry Server "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "CRR",
        "answer": "Cross Region Replication ",
        "distractors": [
          "Control Region Resource ",
          "Capacity Repository Repository ",
          "Control Replication Replication "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "CI/CD",
        "answer": "Continuous Integration/Continuous Deployment ",
        "distractors": [
          "Control Interface Datagrams ",
          "Computer Interface Denial ",
          "Check Inter-Domain Disk "
        ]
      }
    ],
    "d": [
      {
        "question": "DMS",
        "answer": "Database Migration Service ",
        "distractors": [
          "Directory Machine Sign-On ",
          "Delivery Memory S3 ",
          "Directory Machine Scaling "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "DNS",
        "answer": "Domain Name System ",
        "distractors": [
          "Database Network Socket ",
          "Datagrams Network Storage ",
          "Directory Name Service "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "DDoS",
        "answer": "Distributed Denial of Service ",
        "distractors": [
          "Design Data S3 ",
          "Data Design Second ",
          "Deployment Disk Storage "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "DoS",
        "answer": "Denial of Service ",
        "distractors": [
          "Denial Service ",
          "Development Second ",
          "Deployment Storage "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "DaaS",
        "answer": "Desktop as-a-Service ",
        "distractors": [
          "Design as-a-Service ",
          "Disk as-a-Service ",
          "Disk as-a-Service "
        ]
      }
    ],
    "e": [
      {
        "question": "EC2",
        "answer": "Elastic Compute Cloud ",
        "distractors": [
          "Encryption Control Cloud ",
          "Email Cloud Client ",
          "Email Compute Control "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "ECS",
        "answer": "EC2 Container Service ",
        "distractors": [
          "Email Control Security ",
          "Encryption Container Side ",
          "Encryption Capacity System "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "ECR",
        "answer": "Elastic Container Registry ",
        "distractors": [
          "Encryption Certificate Resource ",
          "Emulator Check Redundancy ",
          "Emulator Cloud Reliable "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "EFS",
        "answer": "Elastic File System ",
        "distractors": [
          "Extensions Firewall Service ",
          "Encryption Fabric System ",
          "Encryption First System "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "EI",
        "answer": "Elastic Inference ",
        "distractors": [
          "Encryption Interface ",
          "Express Interface ",
          "Encryption Inference "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "ENA",
        "answer": "Elastic Network Adapter ",
        "distractors": [
          "Encryption Network Array ",
          "Encryption Network Access ",
          "Express Name Access "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "EKS",
        "answer": "Elastic Kubernetes Service ",
        "distractors": [
          "Extensions Kit Service ",
          "Encryption Kubernetes Service ",
          "Encryption Kit Service "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "EBS",
        "answer": "Elastic Block Store ",
        "distractors": [
          "Express Balancer Scaling ",
          "Encryption Balancing Service ",
          "Encryption Balancer System "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "EMR",
        "answer": "Elastic MapReduce ",
        "distractors": [
          "Encryption Machine ",
          "Encryption Migration ",
          "Express MapReduce "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "ELB",
        "answer": "Elastic Load Balancing ",
        "distractors": [
          "Encryption Load Balancer ",
          "Encryption License Balancer ",
          "Extensions Layer Balancer "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "EFA",
        "answer": "Elastic Fabric Adapter ",
        "distractors": [
          "Email Fabric Address ",
          "Emulator Firewall Analytics ",
          "Express First Adapter "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "EIP",
        "answer": "Elastic IP ",
        "distractors": [
          "Elastic Instance Provisioning",
          "Enhanced IP Protocol",
          "External Internet Pathway"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "EDA",
        "answer": "Electronic Design Automation ",
        "distractors": [
          "Express Data Attack ",
          "Emulator Design Agreement ",
          "Extensions Design Access "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "ENI",
        "answer": "Elastic Network Interface ",
        "distractors": [
          "Encryption Network Integration/Continuous ",
          "Encryption Name Interface ",
          "Encryption Network Interface "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "ECU",
        "answer": "EC2 Compute Unit ",
        "distractors": [
          "Encryption Container Unit ",
          "Emulator Control Unit ",
          "Encryption Control Unit "
        ]
      }
    ],
    "f": [
      {
        "question": "FIFO",
        "answer": "First In First Out ",
        "distractors": [
          "Firewall First Object ",
          "File Federation Origin ",
          "First Fabric Out "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "FaaS",
        "answer": "Function as-a-Service ",
        "distractors": [
          "Federation as-a-Service ",
          "Federation as ",
          "Federation as "
        ]
      }
    ],
    "h": [
      {
        "question": "HPC",
        "answer": "High-Performance Compute ",
        "distractors": [
          "undefined Client ",
          "undefined Compute ",
          "undefined Compute "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "HVM",
        "answer": "Hardware Virtual Machine ",
        "distractors": [
          "undefined Virtual Memory ",
          "undefined Vector Management ",
          "undefined Virtual Machine "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "HTTP",
        "answer": "Hypertext Transfer Protocol ",
        "distractors": [
          "undefined Things Per ",
          "undefined Translation Programming ",
          "undefined Transfer Processing "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "HTTPS",
        "answer": "HTTP Secure ",
        "distractors": [
          "undefined System ",
          "undefined System ",
          "undefined Service "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "HDK",
        "answer": "Hardware Development Kit ",
        "distractors": [
          "undefined Directory Kit ",
          "undefined Disk Kit ",
          "undefined Development Kubernetes "
        ]
      }
    ],
    "i": [
      {
        "question": "IAM",
        "answer": "Identity & Access Management ",
        "distractors": [
          "Intelligence Array Management ",
          "Initiative Address Management ",
          "Image Automation Memory "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "iOT",
        "answer": "Internet Of Things ",
        "distractors": [
          "Integration/Continuous Transfer ",
          "Intelligence To ",
          "In Transaction "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "S3 IA",
        "answer": "S3 Infrequent Access ",
        "distractors": [
          "Intelligence Analytics ",
          "IP Access ",
          "Inference Area "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "iSCSI",
        "answer": "Internet Small Computer Storage Interface ",
        "distractors": [
          "Industry Side Control Standard Intelligence ",
          "Integration/Continuous Service Compute S3 IP ",
          "Independent Standard Certificate Security Integration/Continuous "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "IOPS",
        "answer": "Input/Output Operation Per Second ",
        "distractors": [
          "Independent Origin Processing Service ",
          "Image Origin Protocol Secure ",
          "Interface Of Processing S3 "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "IGW",
        "answer": "Internet Gateway ",
        "distractors": [
          "Instance Gateway ",
          "Industry Group ",
          "Instance Gateway "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "ICMP",
        "answer": "Internet Control Message Protocol ",
        "distractors": [
          "Industry Control Machine Parallel ",
          "In Container Memory Programming ",
          "Image Capacity Machine PCI "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "IP",
        "answer": "Internet Protocol ",
        "distractors": [
          "Image Protocol ",
          "Inter-Domain Protocol ",
          "Indication Private "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "IPSec",
        "answer": "Internet Protocol Security ",
        "distractors": [
          "Inference Programming Sharing ",
          "Industry Programming Security ",
          "Interface Per Server "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "IaaS",
        "answer": "Infrastructure-as-a-Service ",
        "distractors": [
          "Interface-as-a-Service",
          "Integration-as-a-Service",
          "Information-as-a-Service"
        ]
      }
    ],
    "j": [
      {
        "question": "JSON",
        "answer": "JavaScript Object Notation ",
        "distractors": [
          "undefined Operation Name ",
          "undefined Own Name ",
          "undefined Of Network "
        ]
      }
    ],
    "k": [
      {
        "question": "KMS",
        "answer": "Key Management Service ",
        "distractors": [
          "Kubernetes MapReduce Side ",
          "Kubernetes Markup Secure ",
          "Kit Machine System "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "KVM",
        "answer": "Kernel-based Virtual Machine ",
        "distractors": [
          "Kubernetes Virtual MapReduce ",
          "Kubernetes Vector Migration ",
          "Kit Virtual Machine "
        ]
      }
    ],
    "l": [
      {
        "question": "LB",
        "answer": "Load Balancer ",
        "distractors": [
          "Latency Balancer",
          "Load Buffer",
          "Link Bandwidth"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "LCU",
        "answer": "Load Balancer Capacity Unit ",
        "distractors": [
          "Line Balancer Control Unit ",
          "Layer Balancer Control Unit ",
          "List Balancing Cloud Unit "
        ]
      }
    ],
    "m": [
      {
        "question": "MFA",
        "answer": "Multi-Factor Authentication ",
        "distractors": [
          "Memory Authentication ",
          "Message Assertion ",
          "Markup Analytics "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "MSTSC",
        "answer": "Microsoft Terminal Service Client ",
        "distractors": [
          "Module Token Side Control ",
          "Machine Time Storage Check ",
          "Memory Translation Service Compute "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "MPP",
        "answer": "Massive Parallel Processing ",
        "distractors": [
          "MapReduce Programming Protocol ",
          "Management PCI Policies ",
          "Management Protocol Processing "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "MITM",
        "answer": "Man in the Middle Attack ",
        "distractors": [
          "Module the Memory Access ",
          "Markup the Markup Address ",
          "Module the Memory Assertion "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "MPLS",
        "answer": "Multi Protocol Label Switching ",
        "distractors": [
          "Machine Protocol Language Second ",
          "Machine Programming Line Second ",
          "Manager Protocol Level Service "
        ]
      }
      ,
      {
        "question": "MWAA",
        "answer": "Managed Workflows for Apache Airflow",
        "distractors": [
          "Managed Workflows for Apache Spark",
          "Amazon MWAA Service",
          "AWS Step Functions"
        ]
      }
    ],
    "n": [
      {
        "question": "NFS",
        "answer": "Network File System ",
        "distractors": [
          "Name Federation Server ",
          "Notification Fabric System ",
          "Network Fabric System "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "NS",
        "answer": "Name Server ",
        "distractors": [
          "Name Service ",
          "Name Services ",
          "Network Service "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "NAT",
        "answer": "Network Address Translation ",
        "distractors": [
          "Name Access Token ",
          "Name Amazon Translation ",
          "Network Authentication Translation "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "NVMe",
        "answer": "Non-Volatile Memory Express ",
        "distractors": [
          "Network Migration Encryption ",
          "Notification Memory Encryption ",
          "Network Markup Extensions "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "NLB",
        "answer": "Network Load Balancer ",
        "distractors": [
          "Node Location Broker ",
          "Native Logging Backend ",
          "Networked Logic Bridge "
        ]
      }
    ],
    "o": [
      {
        "question": "OLTP",
        "answer": "Online Transaction Processing ",
        "distractors": [
          "Of Transfer Per ",
          "Of Transfer Parallel ",
          "Of Translation Programming "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "OLAP",
        "answer": "Online Analytics Processing ",
        "distractors": [
          "Own Address Policies ",
          "Own Amazon Processing ",
          "Out Analysis Protocol "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "OCI",
        "answer": "Open Container Initiative ",
        "distractors": [
          "Own Control Interface ",
          "Out Control Interface ",
          "Own Client Integration/Continuous "
        ]
      }
    ],
    "p": [
      {
        "question": "PCI DSS",
        "answer": "Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard ",
        "distractors": [
          "Per Container Interface Data Security Storage ",
          "Platform Cloud Industry Design Storage Service ",
          "PCI Check Image Development Service Switching "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "PVM",
        "answer": "Para Virtual Machine ",
        "distractors": [
          "Private Virtual Memory ",
          "Private Virtual MapReduce ",
          "Private Virtual Machine "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "PV",
        "answer": "ParaVirtual ",
        "distractors": [
          "Partial Virtualization",
          "Provisioned Volume",
          "Private VLAN"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "PaaS",
        "answer": "Platform as a Service ",
        "distractors": [
          "Policies Shell ",
          "Processing Service ",
          "Protocol Service "
        ]
      }
    ],
    "r": [
      {
        "question": "RAID",
        "answer": "Redundant Array of Independent Disk ",
        "distractors": [
          "Replication Assertion Image Design ",
          "Repository Application Interface Design ",
          "Registry Area IP Design "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "RDS",
        "answer": "Relational Database Service ",
        "distractors": [
          "Region Design System ",
          "Redundancy Disk Service ",
          "Resource Database System "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "RRS",
        "answer": "Reduced Redundancy Storage ",
        "distractors": [
          "Registry Region Small ",
          "Resource Resource System ",
          "Resource Routing Service "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "RI",
        "answer": "Reserved Instance ",
        "distractors": [
          "Reliable Intelligence ",
          "Resource Image ",
          "Resource Interface "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "RAM",
        "answer": "Random-access Memory ",
        "distractors": [
          "Repository Message ",
          "Registry Message ",
          "Registry Machine "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "RIE",
        "answer": "Runtime Interface Emulator ",
        "distractors": [
          "Registry Infrastructure Express ",
          "Registry Initiative Express ",
          "Resource Interface Email "
        ]
      }
    ],
    "s": [
      {
        "question": "SSE",
        "answer": "Server Side Encryption ",
        "distractors": [
          "Service Service Encryption ",
          "Scaling Sign-On Encryption ",
          "Service Storage Express "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "S3",
        "answer": "Simple Storage Service ",
        "distractors": [
          "Service System Side ",
          "Services Security System ",
          "Service Service Service "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "S3 RTC",
        "answer": "S3 Replication Time Control ",
        "distractors": [
          "Routing Token Capacity ",
          "Routing Transfer Check ",
          "Redundancy Token Control "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "SRR",
        "answer": "Same Region Replication ",
        "distractors": [
          "Scaling Reliable Reliable ",
          "S3 Region Redundancy ",
          "System Registry Routing "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "SMS",
        "answer": "Server Migration Service ",
        "distractors": [
          "System Machine System ",
          "Server Machine Services ",
          "Scaling Management Service "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "SWF",
        "answer": "Simple Workflow Service ",
        "distractors": [
          "Security Workflow Side ",
          "Services Workflow Storage ",
          "Switching Web Security "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "SES",
        "answer": "Simple Email Service ",
        "distractors": [
          "Service Emulator Storage ",
          "Switching Express Secure ",
          "Service Encryption Service "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "SNS",
        "answer": "Simple Notification Service ",
        "distractors": [
          "Service Network Service ",
          "Storage Name System ",
          "System Notification Side "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "SQS",
        "answer": "Simple Queue Service ",
        "distractors": [
          "Second Queue Service ",
          "Second Queue Security ",
          "Side Queue Security "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "SES",
        "answer": "Simple Email Service ",
        "distractors": [
          "Scaling Email Storage ",
          "Sign-On Extensions Socket ",
          "Sign-On Email System "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "SLA",
        "answer": "Service Level Agreement ",
        "distractors": [
          "Standard License Authority ",
          "Scaling Language Address ",
          "Services Layer Agreement "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "SSL",
        "answer": "Secure Socket Layer ",
        "distractors": [
          "Secure Service Level ",
          "Service Service License ",
          "Storage Small List "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "SOA",
        "answer": "Start of Authority ",
        "distractors": [
          "Service Oriented Architecture ",
          "Secure Operations Administration ",
          "System Orchestration Automation "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "SDK",
        "answer": "Software Development Kit ",
        "distractors": [
          "Sign-On Database Kit ",
          "System Development Kubernetes ",
          "Services Database Kubernetes "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "SSH",
        "answer": "Secure Shell ",
        "distractors": [
          "Service Store ",
          "Service Standard ",
          "System Standard "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "SAR",
        "answer": "Serverless Application Repository ",
        "distractors": [
          "Service Address Redundancy ",
          "Sharing Adapter Redundancy ",
          "S3 Adapter Resource "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "SRD",
        "answer": "Scalable Reliable Datagrams ",
        "distractors": [
          "Storage Reliable Denial ",
          "Service Replication Data ",
          "Security Resource Database "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "SSO",
        "answer": "Single Sign-On ",
        "distractors": [
          "Single Service Object",
          "Secure Sign-On",
          "Shared Session Option"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "SAML",
        "answer": "Security Assertion Markup Language ",
        "distractors": [
          "Service Attack Machine Load ",
          "Service Authentication Migration Load ",
          "Service Adapter Management Layer "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "SaaS",
        "answer": "Software-as-a-Service ",
        "distractors": [
          "System-as-a-Service Architecture",
          "Storage-as-a-Service Application",
          "Solutions-as-a-Service Platform"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "SaaS",
        "answer": "Security-as-a-Service ",
        "distractors": [
          "Service ",
          "Service ",
          "Security "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "SCP",
        "answer": "Service Control Policies ",
        "distractors": [
          "Service Compute Per ",
          "Second Check Per ",
          "Sign-On Cloud Protocol "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "SCA",
        "answer": "Storage Class Analysis ",
        "distractors": [
          "Service Compute Analysis ",
          "Security Capacity Array ",
          "Store Compute Amazon "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "STS",
        "answer": "Security Token Service ",
        "distractors": [
          "Service Transfer Service ",
          "Store Token Service ",
          "Service Time Sharing "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "SNI",
        "answer": "Server Name Indication ",
        "distractors": [
          "Storage Name Image ",
          "Storage Name Intelligence ",
          "Sign-On Notification Instance "
        ]
      }
    ],
    "t": [
      {
        "question": "TTL",
        "answer": "Time To Live ",
        "distractors": [
          "Transaction Time Limit",
          "Transmission Timing Layer",
          "Token Time Lock"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "TLS",
        "answer": "Transport Layer Security ",
        "distractors": [
          "Terminal List Service ",
          "Transfer Line Security ",
          "Transfer Load Service "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "TPM",
        "answer": "Trusted Platform Module ",
        "distractors": [
          "Transfer Protocol Machine ",
          "Transfer Per Module ",
          "Terminal Protocol Management "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "TME",
        "answer": "Total Memory Encryption ",
        "distractors": [
          "Tape Management Encryption ",
          "Token Machine Emulator ",
          "Transfer Migration Email "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "TPM",
        "answer": "Technical Program Manager ",
        "distractors": [
          "Transfer Processing Migration ",
          "Transaction Programming Management ",
          "Translation Platform Markup "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "TPS",
        "answer": "Transaction Per Second ",
        "distractors": [
          "Transaction Processing Small ",
          "To Processing Shell ",
          "Time Processing Services "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "TCP",
        "answer": "Transmission Control Protocol ",
        "distractors": [
          "Time Compute Protocol ",
          "Translation Container Processing ",
          "Translation Control Per "
        ]
      }
    ],
    "v": [
      {
        "question": "VPC",
        "answer": "Virtual Private Cloud ",
        "distractors": [
          "Vector Policies Container ",
          "Virtual Processing Capacity ",
          "Virtual Protocol Control "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "VM",
        "answer": "Virtual Machine ",
        "distractors": [
          "Vector Management ",
          "Virtual Machine ",
          "Vector Machine "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "VTL",
        "answer": "Virtual Tape Library ",
        "distractors": [
          "Virtual Things Library ",
          "Virtual Translation Load ",
          "Vector To Library "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "VPN",
        "answer": "Virtual Private Network ",
        "distractors": [
          "Vector Parallel Network ",
          "Virtual Programming Name ",
          "Virtual PCI Network "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "VLAN",
        "answer": "Virtual Local Area Network ",
        "distractors": [
          "Virtual License Analytics Network ",
          "Vector Library Area Notation ",
          "Virtual Line Automation Name "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "VDI",
        "answer": "Virtual Desktop Infrastructure ",
        "distractors": [
          "Virtual Desktop Initiative ",
          "Virtual Directory Integration/Continuous ",
          "Vector Deployment Inference "
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "VPG",
        "answer": "Virtual Private Gateway ",
        "distractors": [
          "Virtual Programming Group ",
          "Vector Protocol Gateway ",
          "Virtual Processing Group "
        ]
      }
    ],
    "w": [
      {
        "question": "WAF",
        "answer": "Web Application Firewall",
        "distractors": [
          "Web Assertion Federation ",
          "Workflow Automation File ",
          "Workflow Adapter File "
        ]
      }
    ],
    "generative_ai": [
      {
          "question": "Train, tune, and deploy machine learning models at scale",
          "answer": "Amazon SageMaker",
          "distractors": [
              "AWS Lambda",
              "Amazon Textract",
              "AWS AppSync"
          ]
      },
      {
          "question": "AWS chip designed for high-performance AI model training",
          "answer": "AWS Trainium (Trainium2)",
          "distractors": [
              "AWS Inferentia2",
              "Amazon Kinesis",
              "Amazon Aurora"
          ]
      },
      {
          "question": "AWS chip optimized for deep learning inference workloads",
          "answer": "AWS Inferentia2",
          "distractors": [
              "AWS Trainium (Trainium2)",
              "Amazon Redshift",
              "AWS Wavelength"
          ]
      },
      {
          "question": "Multimodal foundation model accessible via Amazon Bedrock",
          "answer": "Amazon Titan",
          "distractors": [
              "Amazon Neptune",
              "Amazon Rekognition",
              "AWS Snowcone"
          ]
      },
      {
          "question": "AI assistant for writing code, querying data, and using AWS services",
          "answer": "Amazon CodeWhisperer",
          "distractors": [
              "AWS Copilot",
              "Amazon WorkDocs",
              "Amazon Translate"
          ]
      },
      {
          "question": "Automate code reviews and identify expensive lines of code",
          "answer": "Amazon CodeGuru",
          "distractors": [
              "Amazon Lex",
              "AWS Cloud9",
              "Amazon Comprehend"
          ]
      },

      {
        "question": "Fully managed service for foundation models from multiple providers",
        "answer": "Amazon Bedrock",
        "distractors": [
          "Amazon SageMaker",
          "AWS Lambda",
          "Amazon Comprehend"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "AI assistant for AWS services and cloud operations",
        "answer": "Amazon Q Business",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS Chatbot",
          "Amazon Lex",
          "Amazon CodeWhisperer"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "AI service for medical transcription and documentation",
        "answer": "AWS HealthScribe",
        "distractors": [
          "Amazon Transcribe",
          "Amazon Comprehend Medical",
          "AWS HealthLake"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "AI-powered call center analytics service",
        "answer": "Amazon Transcribe Call Analytics",
        "distractors": [
          "Amazon Connect",
          "Amazon Lex",
          "Contact Lens for Amazon Connect"
        ]
      }
    ],
    "data_and_analytics": [
      {
        "question": "Collaborative data analysis with multiple parties",
        "answer": "AWS Clean Rooms",
        "distractors": [
          "Amazon QuickSight",
          "AWS Lake Formation",
          "Amazon Athena"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Data management and governance service",
        "answer": "Amazon DataZone",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS Glue",
          "Amazon Redshift",
          "AWS Lake Formation"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Serverless search and analytics service",
        "answer": "Amazon OpenSearch Serverless",
        "distractors": [
          "Amazon OpenSearch Service",
          "Amazon CloudSearch",
          "Amazon Kendra"
        ]
      }
    ],
    "other": [
      {
        "question": "Spatial simulation service for large-scale simulations",
        "answer": "AWS SimSpace Weaver",
        "distractors": [
          "Amazon Sumerian",
          "AWS RoboMaker",
          "Amazon GameLift"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Supply chain management and optimization",
        "answer": "AWS Supply Chain",
        "distractors": [
          "Amazon Forecast",
          "AWS IoT SiteWise",
          "Amazon Connect"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "AI-powered medical image analysis",
        "answer": "AWS HealthImaging",
        "distractors": [
          "Amazon Comprehend Medical",
          "Amazon Transcribe Medical",
          "AWS HealthLake"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Explore and experiment with quantum computing",
        "answer": "Amazon Braket",
        "distractors": [
          "AWS Data Pipeline",
          "AWS DeepLens",
          "AWS Console Mobile Application"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Fully managed ground station as a service",
        "answer": "AWS Ground Station",
        "distractors": [
          "Amazon EC2 Auto Scaling",
          "Amazon EMR",
          "AWS Elemental MediaStore"
        ]
      }
    ]
  }
}